http://www.bhwp.org/privacy/

About Native Plants
What is a Native Plant?
What is a Plant Community?
Why are Native Plants and Plant Communities Important?
Invasive Species
What Threats Do Invasives Pose to Our Native Plant Communities?
Become a Naturalist
What is a Naturalist?
Levels of Membership
Join Now!
Online Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting Bowman’s Hill Wildflower Preserve's web site. Ethical standards and principles are the foundation for maintaining public trust. Bowman’s Hill Wildflower Preserve takes your privacy seriously and treats all financial and personal information about any transaction you have with the Preserve as highly confidential.
Bowman's Hill Wildflower Preserve is committed to protecting your privacy and will never sell your name, address or other information to anyone. We have created this online privacy policy to explain our commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.
About Your Privacy
Bowman’s Hill Wildflower Preserve does not share donor, constituent and/or prospect information, such as contributions, addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, business information, etc. Database records and all associated lists and reports are confidential and the property of Bowman’s Hill Wildflower Preserve.
This Bill of Rights for charitable givers was developed by the following four industry experts: the American Association of Fund Raising Counsel, Association for Healthcare Philanthropy, Council for Advancement and Support of Education, and National Society of Fund Raising Executives. The Preserve endorses this industry-accepted policy.
Bowman’s Hill Wildflower Preserve collects information from site visitors at several different points on this website. This notice applies to all information collected by or submitted to our websites. On some pages, you can opt in to receive email communications, register for events, or send communications to our staff.
The types of personal information collected on these pages varies and can include:
Name of member or visitor
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit Card Information
If you do submit personal information to us, we will use that information for the purposes for which it was submitted including:
If you join our email list, we will have a record of your email address. We may send you occasional emails about our events or activities, as well as any specific issues or publications you have subscribed to. You will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from our mailing list.
If you sign up for or renew a Bowman’s Hill Wildflower Preserve membership, your personal information will be used to fulfill the financial transaction you have initiated, and your information will be added to our database for communication and maintenance regarding your membership.
Links to other Websites
This website may contain links to other websites for partner organizations, sponsors and additional products and services. Bowman’s Hill Wildflower Preserve is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
If you are concerned about how your information is used, please contact us with questions:Bowman’s Hill Wildflower PreservePO Box 685New Hope, PA 18938215.862.2924or by e-mail at bhwp@bhwp.org
Restrictions of Use
This site is owned and operated by Bowman’s Hill Wildflower Preserve. Materials found on this website may be used for non-commercial use only, providing all copyright and other proprietary notices are kept intact. You may not alter or attempt to alter any materials or information on the site, or the site itself. Linking to bhwp.org is acceptable and encouraged.
Make a donation to the Preserve today
Donate Now
Help support all of our work
Become a member today!
Join today
Membership includes admission to the Preserve and more!
